Seid Zerihun

Full stuck web developer

E-mail: seidoo99@gmail.com github: github.com/seidoo99 phone: 240-423-6866

Personal Profile

I'm a Full Stack Web Developer living in Atlanta, GA. I graduated my bachelor degree with major in engineering. I spent the last three years working as automation tester with programming language like java and javascript. As of now I am attending DigitalCrafts' six month, partime flex coding bootcamp and persuing a new challenge as full stack developer.

Featured Projects

Trip App

May 2020

• liveSite: https://tripapp-project.herokuapp.com/login

clear_dark sky

March 2020

• repository: https://github.com/seidoo99/clear-dark-sky-frontend-project

Work Experience

Digital crafts full stuck bootcamp student

January 2020 - present

- 6 month flex part time web development bootcamp
- Daily activities include responsive site design and development, efficient coding, pair programming, debugging, problem solving and version control.

Quality assurance engineer

september 2018 - present

- Perform functional, regression and integration testing of web based, POS and mobile applications involved in testing applications of different platforms such as IOS and android devices
- Created and maintain UI/API automation tests on the Cucumber/Selenium/JavaScript framework for UI automation and mocha/chai/nodeJs framework for API

Automation Tester

september 2017 - August 2018

- Created automation test scripts for the corresponding test cases using selenium Web driver with java.
- Execute SQL and elastic search queries in the database to conduct data integrity testing by checking the data tables on the server.

1/2 127.0.0.1:5500/index.html

Key Skills

HTML5/ CSS3 Javascript Java Express NodeJS PostgresSQL/SQL React/redux jquerry Testing tools

Education

University of Bahirdar

BS Chemical engineering

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html